Guide to the Records of the Institute of African American Affairs RG.9.8
New York University Archives
- Series I: Events Files, 61505
  - "Kwanza Celebration", Dec 7, 1987; 61563 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Dr. Martin Luther King, Jr. Reception, Jan 19, 1988; 61562 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Recovering the Lost Treasures of Africa: A Lecture by Dr. Ekpo Eyo, Feb 4, 1988; 61561 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - A Tribute to James Baldwin, Feb 29, 1988-Mar 1, 1988; 61560 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - "Afro-Americans & the Evolution of a Living Constitution" Teleconference, 1988; 61559 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Malumbo Ntshilontshilo, Speaking engagement "Stop the Executions of the South African Youth Tour," Cosponsored by IAAA & Young Socialist Alliance Student Organization at NYU, 1988; 61558 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226024 3
  - "Caribbean Empowerment in the 21st Century and Beyond", Jun 11, 1988; 61557 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - "The Bicentennial of the U.S. Constitution: Reflections on the Black Experience,", 1988; 61556 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Black History Month Telecast, Feb 1, 1989; 61555 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Black Authors at NYU - Speaking on Their Works, 2/23/89, Oct 11, 1989-Aug 18, 1989; 61554 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Black Indians: A Hidden Heritage; Lecture by Prof. William L. Katz, Mar 29, 1989; 61553 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Lecture-Chinua Achebe, Apr 13, 1989; 61552 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - The Faculty Roundtable Series, Women's Movement, undated; 61551 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - The Prospect for Civilian Democracy in Nigeria, 1990-1992; 61550 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Youth Revolts and the Prospects of Revolution in South Africa, by Dr. Baruch Hirson, Glascow University, Nov 14, 1989; 61549 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Swahili Lecture/Performance of Song and Poetry, Nov 16, 1989; 61548 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Ethnic Diversity and Racial Consciousness in Brazil, Zumbi Conference, Nov 20, 1989; 61547 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Professor Claudine Brown - Gallatin Division, "Social Responsibilities In Museum Planning", Dec 12, 1989; 61546 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - "The Restoration of African History - The Role of Egypt," by Dr. Yosef B. Hochannan, Feb 5, 1990; 61545 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - "The Americana Paper Trail: The Untold African American Legacy," Dwayne D. Key, Speaker, 1990; 61544 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - African Heritage Month, Feb. 1990, 61543 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - "African Roots in Latino Culture," by Marta Moreno Vega, Feb 6, 1990; 61542 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - "Blacks in Science," by Dr. Ivan Van Sertima, Feb 8, 1990; 61541 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - "Castro, the Blacks, and Africa," by Dr. Carlos Moore, Feb 12, 1990; 61540 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Moore, Dr. Carlos, Ben Snow, Feb 12, 1990; 61539 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - "African American Heroes in American Culture," Performed by Rod Rogers Dance Company, Feb 15, 1990; 61538 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Rod Rogers Dance Company, Feb 15, 1990; 61537 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - "Miles" A Biography of Miles Davis: Discussion by Quincy Troupe, an Author, Feb 21, 1990; 61536 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Quincy Troupe, Feb 21, 1990; 61535 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - NYU Faculty Colloquium on Orality, Writing, and Culture, Feb 21, 1990; 61534 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - "The African-American Scholar: Choosing a Life of Learning", Feb 22, 1990; 61533 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - "Mother, Sister, Chile," choreopoem by AWAMU, Mar 21, 1990-Mar 24, 1990; 61532 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - "The Intersection of Race, Gender, and Class in the Health Professions", Mar 29, 1990; 61531 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - African American Graduate Students Public Policy Symposium, Robert F. Wagner Grad. Schl. of Public Svc.-NYU, Apr 5, 1990; 61530 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - "Black Church in America", May 3, 1990; 61529 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Kofi Anyidoho: Poetry Reading, Nov 9, 1990; 61528 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Revelation's Exhibition: Francine Fels, Feb 1, 1991; 61527 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - "The Role of the N.Y.C. Police Dept. in Minority Communities," Black History Month Reception & Lecture, Feb 5, 1991; 61526 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Clark Terry Quartet-Jazz Pg., Feb 19, 1991; 61525 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - "Breaking the Chains: African American Slave Resistance," A Book Presentation/Lecture/Reception/Loren Katz-Spkr., Feb 19, 1991; 61524 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Women's History Month: Hazel Carby-Lecturer, Mar 7, 1991; 61523 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - "300 Years Plus of African American Artifacts & Folk Art," A 2 Day African American Exhibition: Duane Keyes-Dalcour Art Enterprise, Mar 8, 1991-Mar 9, 1991; 61522 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - "Race, Gender and Representation," Lecture by Bell Hooks, Mar 26, 1991; 61521 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Film Screening & Reception: "Keep on Moving," by AWAMU, Apr 6, 1991; 61520 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Black Alumni Association, [EMPTY], Apr 6, 1991; 61519 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Blacks in the Media, Apr 11, 1991; 61518 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226025 0
  - Queens, Queen Mothers, Priestesses, and Power: Case Studies in African Gender: Conference, Correspondence (1), Apr 8, 1991-Apr 10, 1991; 61517 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Queens, Queen Mothers, Priestesses, and Power: Case Studies in African Gender: Conference; Correspondence (2), [EMPTY], Apr 8, 1991-Apr 10, 1991; 61516 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Queens, Queen Mothers, Priestesses, and Power; Forms, Apr 8, 1991-Apr 10, 1991; 61515 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Queens, Queen Mothers, Priestesses, and Power: Case Studies in African Gender: Conference Programming, Planning, Etc., Apr 8, 1991-Apr 10, 1991; 61514 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Queens, Queen Mothers, Priestesses, and Power: Case Studies in African Gender: Conference Publicity, Apr 8, 1991-Apr 10, 1991; 61513 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - "Kongo Carolina, Kongo New Orleans: Notes on a Major Transatlantic Art Tradition," Lecturer - Robert F. Thompson, Apr 16, 1991; 61512 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Minority Journalist Society Lecture-Guest Speaker Gil Noble, Apr 30, 1991; 61511 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - African American & Latino Awards Ceremony, May 1, 1991; 61510 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Great Zimbabwe Cross-cultural Reception: "The Best of Zimbabwe Display", May 19, 1991; 61509 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - [Untitled folder containing material on Francine Fels' exhibit "Happy Birthday, Rev!"], May 28, 1991-Jul 2, 1991; 61508 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Francine Fels, undated; 61507 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - "Happy Birthday, Rev!" Tribute to Alvin Ailey, undated; 61506 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - June 2018 Accretion, 1995-1999 (Box 81, Folder 1-58, Box 82, Folder 1-34, Box 83, Folder 1-21, Box 59, Folder 1-9)
  - Event Material, 1993-2018 (Box 101, Folder 1-22, Box 102, Folder 1-15, Box 103, Folder 1-13)
  - Black Renaissance Noire, 1994-2015 (Box 104, Folder 1-14, Box 105, Folder 1-5, Box 106, Folder 1-6, Box 107, Box 108, Box 109, Box 110, Box 111, Folder 1-2)
- Series II: Association for Education in Journalism (AEJ), 61188
  - Class Arrangements - AEJ, 1970; 61504 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226025 1
  - Correspondence - AEJ, 1970; 61503 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Finances - AEJ, 1970; 61502 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Forms - AEJ, 1970; 61501 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Magazines - AEJ, 1970; 61500 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Class Arrangements - AEJ, 1971; 61499 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence - AEJ, 1971; 61498 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - AEJ Correspondence, 1971; 61497 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Final Report - AEJ, 1971; 61496 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Finances - AEJ, 1971; 61495 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Forms - AEJ, 1971; 61494 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Magazines - AEJ, 1971; 61493 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Miscellaneous - AEJ, 1971; 61492 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence - AEJ, 1972; 61491 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Finances - AEJ, 1972; 61490 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Forms - AEJ, 1972; 61489 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Magazines - AEJ, 1972; 61488 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Hamilton, William P., Intern, 1972; 61487 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Hearn, Sandra, Intern, 1972; 61486 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Mangual, Anna, Intern, 1972; 61485 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Morris, Burnice Mr., Intern, 1972; 61484 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Newton, Linda L., Intern, 1972; 61483 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Reddix, Brenda R., Intern, 1972; 61482 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - West, Charles, Intern, 1972; 61481 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Class Arrangements - AEJ, 1973; 61480 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Correspondence - AEJ (1), 1973; 61479 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Correspondence - AEJ (2), 1973; 61478 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Finances - AEJ, 1973; 61477 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Forms - AEJ, 1973; 61476 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226026 8
  - Magazines - AEJ, 1973; 61475 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous - AEJ, 1973; 61474 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Program Operations - AEJ, 1973; 61473 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Receptions - AEJ, 1973; 61472 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - AEJ Tapes, 73 [envelope]; Tapes of A.E.J. "Journalism & Minorities" Seminar, 1973; 61471 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Burrell, Judy, Intern, undated; 61470 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Chunn, Kelley, undated; 61469 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Clark, Anthony J., undated; 61468 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - De Graffenreidt, James, undated; 61467 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Dorothy Langhorne, undated; 61466 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Mitchell, Robert, undated; 61465 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Montemayor, Robert, undated; 61464 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Walters, Barbara, undated; 61463 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Class Arrangements - AEJ, 1974; 61462 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence - AEJ, 1974; 61461 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Final Report - AEJ, 1974; 61460 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Forms - AEJ, 1974; 61459 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Receptions - AEJ, 1974; 61458 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Program Operation - AEJ, 1974; 61457 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Asselin, Charles, A+, 1974; 61456 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Braithwaite, Colleen R., A-, 1974; 61455 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Brooks, Rodney, A-, 1974; 61454 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Burton, Charlene F., A+, 1974; 61453 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Calahan, Hortense C. A+, 1974; 61452 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Cerna, Henry James, 1974; 61451 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Prentice Favors, 1974; 61450 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - French, Roberta, A++, 1974; 61449 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Jones, Wendy Dianna, A-, 1974; 61448 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Richardson, Kenneth, B+, 1974; 61447 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Thompson, Rodney, A, 1974; 61446 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Class Arrangements - AEJ, 1975; 61445 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence - AEJ, 1975; 61444 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Final Report - AEJ, 1975; 61443 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Finances - AEJ, 1975; 61442 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Forms - AEJ, 1975; 61441 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Magazines - AEJ, 1975; 61440 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Receptions - AEJ, 1975; 61439 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - AEJ Finalists/Interns; Marshall Boyd, 1975; 61438 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - AEJ Finalists/Interns; Donna Britt, 1975; 61437 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - AEJ Finalists/Interns; Aubrey Calloway, 1975; 61436 (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - AEJ Finalists/Interns; James Hadley, 1975; 61435 (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - AEJ Finalists/Interns; Cecilian Fernandez, 1975; 61434 (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - AEJ Finalists/Interns; Gazelia Payne, 1975; 61433 (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - AEJ Finalists/Interns; Tonya Widemon, 1975; 61432 (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Class Arrangements - AEJ, 1975; 61431 (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - Correspondence - AEJ, 1976; 61430 (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - Final Report - AEJ, 1976; 61429 (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Finances - AEJ, 1976; 61428 (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - Forms - AEJ, 1976; 61427 (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - Magazines - AEJ, 1976; 61426 (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - AEJ Finalists/Interns; Joseph Fugett, 1976; 61425 (Box 9, Folder 53)
  - AEJ Finalists/Interns; Sandra Gregg, 1976; 61424 (Box 9, Folder 54)
  - AEJ Finalists/Interns; Valerie Kersey, 1976; 61423 (Box 9, Folder 55)
  - AEJ Finalists/Interns; Raymond Patterson, 1976; 61422 (Box 9, Folder 56)
  - AEJ Finalists/Interns; Debra Marie Martin, 1976; 61421 (Box 9, Folder 57)
  - AEJ Finalists/Interns; Robert Palomares, 1976; 61420 (Box 9, Folder 58)
  - AEJ Finalists/Interns; Velma Thomas, 1976; 61419 (Box 9, Folder 59)
  - AEJ Finalists/Interns; Sheilah Diane Vance, 1976; 61418 (Box 9, Folder 60)
  - Class Arrangements - AEJ, 1977; 61417 (Box 9, Folder 61)
  - Correspondence AEJ (1), 1977; 61416 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence AEJ (2), 1977; 61415 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226027 6
  - Final Report AEJ, 1977; 61414 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Finances AEJ, 1977; 61413 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Forms AEJ, 1977; 61412 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Magazines - AEJ, 1977; 61411 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous - AEJ, 1977; 61410 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Program Operation - AEJ, 1977; 61409 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Receptions - AEJ, 1977; 61408 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - AEJ Finalists/Interns: Ronald Daise, 1977; 61407 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - AEJ Finalists/Interns: Sundra Escott, 1977; 61406 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - AEJ Finalists/Interns: Lydia Gardner, 1977; 61405 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - AEJ Finalists/Interns: Mr. Tracey Gibson, 1977; 61404 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - AEJ Finalists/Interns: Sheryl Hilliard, 1977; 61403 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - AEJ Finalists/Interns: Kenneth Myers, 1977; 61402 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - AEJ Finalists/Interns: Roslyn Smackum, 1977; 61401 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - AEJ Finalists/Interns: M. Patricia Yu, 1977; 61400 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Class Arrangements - AEJ, 1978; 61399 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence - AEJ (1), 1978; 61398 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence - AEJ (2), 1978; 61397 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Final Report - AEJ, 1978; 61396 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Finances - AEJ, 1978; 61395 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Forms - AEJ, 1978; 61394 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Magazines - AEJ, 1978; 61393 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Program Operation - AEJ, 1978; 61392 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Receptions - AEJ, 1978; 61391 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - AEJ Interns: Abdul-Azeez, Suleiman, 1978; 61390 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - AEJ Interns: Branch, George E., 1978; 61389 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - AEJ Interns: Cage, Mary, 1978; 61388 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - AEJ Interns: Clayton, Gail, 1978; 61387 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - AEJ Interns: Dannells, Vernyce, 1978; 61386 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - AEJ Interns: Duckett, Joy, 1978; 61385 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - AEJ Interns: Morgan, Viola J., 1978; 61384 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - AEJ Interns: Navarro, Mireya, 1978; 61383 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - AEJ Interns: Owens, Previa M., 1978; 61382 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - AEJ Interns: Robinson, Glynis, 1978; 61381 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - AEJ Interns: Robotham, Rosemarie, 1978; 61380 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - AEJ Interns: Saxon, Janet, 1978; 61379 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Class Arrangements - AEJ, 1979; 61378 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Correspondence - AEJ (1), 1979; 61377 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Correspondence - AEJ (2), 1979; 61376 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Final Report - AEJ, 1979; 61375 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Finances - AEJ, 1979; 61374 (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Forms - AEJ, 1979; 61373 (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Magazines - AEJ, 1979; 61372 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Receptions - AEJ, 1979; 61371 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226028 4
  - AEJ Summer Interns: Anderson, Janet M., 1979; 61370 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - AEJ Summer Interns: Anderson, Kathy Renee, 1979; 61369 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - AEJ Summer Interns: Beach-Wilson, Gladys, 1979; 61368 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - AEJ Summer Interns: Brown, William T., 1979; 61367 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - AEJ Summer Interns: Camara, Sajo M., 1979; 61366 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - AEJ Summer Interns: Carkum, Shelly, 1979; 61365 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - AEJ Summer Interns: Greth, Carlos, 1979; 61364 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - AEJ Summer Interns: Gwynn, Kathy L., 1979; 61363 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - AEJ Summer Interns: Lecoints, Gertrude, 1979; 61362 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - AEJ Summer Interns: Leonard, Lori A., 1979; 61361 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - AEJ Summer Interns: Magubane, Vukani, 1979; 61360 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - AEJ Summer Interns: Shields, Audrey D., 1979; 61359 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - AEJ Summer Interns: Smith, Robina S., 1979; 61358 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - AEJ Summer Interns: Utsey, Keith J., 1979; 61357 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - AEJ Summer Interns: Wright, Winford C., 1979; 61356 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - AEJ Summer Interns: Vazquez, Carmen A., 1979; 61355 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Class Arrangements - AEJ, 1980; 61354 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence - AEJ (1), 1980; 61353 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence - AEJ (2), 1980; 61352 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence - AEJ (3), 1980; 61351 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Final Report - AEJ, 1980; 61350 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Finances - AEJ, 1980; 61349 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Forms - AEJ, 1980; 61348 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Magazines - AEJ, 1980; 61347 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Program Operation - AEJ, 1980; 61346 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Program Operation - AEJ (1), 1980; 61345 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Program Operation - AEJ (2), 1980; 61344 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Receptions - AEJ, 1980; 61343 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Finalists: Alleyne, Celeste, 1980; 61342 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Finalists: Bailey, Michael, 1980; 61341 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Finalists: Horn, Ginnie, 1980; 61340 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Finalists: Johnson, Cheryl, 1980; 61339 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Finalists: Johnson, Michelle, 1980; 61338 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Finalists: Marrs, Judith, 1980; 61337 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Finalists: Moorehead, Eric, 1980; 61336 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Finalists: Pilcher, Delores, 1980; 61335 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Finalists: Szto, Mary Christine, 1980; 61334 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Finalists: Villarosa, Linda, 1980; 61333 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Finalists: Williams, Kelly, 1980; 61332 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Class Arrangements - AEJ, 1981; 61331 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Correspondence - AEJ (1), 1981; 61330 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Finances - AEJ, 1981; 61329 (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Forms - AEJ, 1981; 61328 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Magazines - AEJ, 1981; 61327 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226029 2
  - Program Administration - AEJ, 1981; 61326 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Program Operation - AEJ, 1981; 61325 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Receptions - AEJ, 1981; 61324 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Interns: Gordon Balkcom, 1981; 61323 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Interns: Jones, Michael, 1981; 61322 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Interns: Martinez, Marcos, 1981; 61321 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Interns: Reeves, Crystal, 1981; 61320 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Interns: Roberts, Sandra, 1981; 61319 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Interns: Rogers, Danita, 1981; 61318 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Interns: Rodriguez, (Jaime) Javier, 1981; 61317 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Interns: Tracey, Aldina, 1981; 61316 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Interns: Trouth, Audrey, 1981; 61315 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Interns: Tuitt, Ronnie, 1982; 61314 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence - AEJ, 1982; 61313 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Finances- AEJ, 1982; 61312 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Final Report - AEJ, 1982; 61311 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Forms - AEJ, 1982; 61310 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Program Operation - AEJ, 1982; 61309 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Interns: Ashley, Berchelle D., 1982; 61308 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Interns: Lily Berjano, 1982; 61307 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Interns: Lisa Bellamy, 1982; 61306 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Interns: Lisa Godley, 1982; 61305 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Interns: Jones, Carla, 1982; 61304 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Interns: Thomas, Larry, 1982; 61303 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Interns: Yvette Walker, 1982; 61302 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Class Arrangements - AEJ, 1983; 61301 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence - AEJ, 1983; 61300 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Final Report - AEJ, 1983; 61299 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Finances - AEJ, 1983; 61298 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Receptions - AEJ, 1983; 61297 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Interns: Adrine, E. Marie, 1983; 61296 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Interns: Collison, Michele, 1983; 61295 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Interns: Goeude, Nicholas, 1983; 61294 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Interns: Hom, Genevieve, 1983; 61293 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Interns: Miller, Deborah, 1983; 61292 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Interns: Seymore, Kelly, 1983; 61291 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Correspondence - AEJ, 1984; 61290 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Forms - AEJ, 1984; 61289 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Interns: Carol Bash, 1984; 61288 (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Interns: Valerie Boyd, 1984; 61287 (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Interns: Leslie Doi, 1984; 61286 (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - Interns: Farah Griffin, 1984; 61285 (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Interns: Joye E. Mercer, 1984; 61284 (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - Interns: Winifred Yu, 1984; 61283 (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - Interns: Lisa V. Bond, 1984; 61282 (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Interns: Adrienne Johnson, 1984; 61281 (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - Interns: Roberto Santiago, 1984; 61280 (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - Interns: Angela L. Slaughter, 1984; 61279 (Box 12, Folder 50)
  - Interns: Wanda Renea Taylor, 1984; 61278 (Box 12, Folder 51)
  - Interns: Vivian S. Toy, 1984; 61277 (Box 12, Folder 52)
  - Class Arrangements - AEJ, 1985; 61276 (Box 12, Folder 53)
  - AEJ Correspondence, 1985; 61275 (Box 12, Folder 54)
  - Correspondence, 1985; 61274 (Box 12, Folder 55)
  - Correspondence - AEJ, 1985; 61273 (Box 12, Folder 56)
  - Final Report - AEJ, 1985; 61272 (Box 12, Folder 57)
  - Finances - AEJ, 1985; 61271 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226030 0
  - Program Operation - AEJ, 1985; 61270 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Receptions - AEJ, 1985; 61269 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Interns: Lisa Best, 1985; 61268 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Interns: Karen Brailsford, 1985; 61267 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Interns: Crystal Hayling, 1985; 61266 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Interns: John C. Hopkins, 1985; 61265 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Interns: Lisa Lewis, 1985; 61264 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Interns: Mai-Lan Pham, 1985; 61263 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Interns: Inez Pinto, 1985; 61262 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Interns: Constance White, 1985; 61261 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Interns: Fredricka Whitfield, 1985; 61260 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Interns: Loretta Williams, 1985; 61259 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Class Arrangements - AEJ, 1986; 61258 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence - AEJ, 1986; 61257 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence - AEJ, 1986; 61256 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Final Report - AEJ, 1986; 61255 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Program Operation - AEJ, 1986; 61254 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Receptions - AEJ, 1986; 61253 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Finalists/Interns: Jennifer Borum, 1986; 61252 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Finalists/Interns: Stephanie Esters, 1986; 61251 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Finalists/Interns: Ernie Freeman, 1986; 61250 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Finalists/Interns: Goodwin, Jesse, 1986; 61249 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Finalists/Interns: Tyrone Guiden, 1986; 61248 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Finalists/Interns: James, Alva Marie, 1986; 61247 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Finalists/Interns: Jeffries, Ira L., 1986; 61246 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Finalists/Interns: Juanita Poe, 1986; 61245 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Finalists/Interns: Salter, Allanah, 1986; 61244 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Finalists/Interns: Tassey, Elaine F., 1986; 61243 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Finalists/Interns: Turner, Dawn, 1986; 61242 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence - AEJ, 1987; 61241 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Finalists: Karen E. Delgado, 1987; 61240 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Finalists: Sheridan Honore, 1987; 61239 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Finalists: Pennie Lee, 1987; 61238 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Finalists: Allison Louis, 1987; 61237 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Finalists: Annette Shaw, 1987; 61236 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Finalists: Smith, Kimberleigh, 1987; 61235 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Finalists: Ayesha Wilson, 1987; 61234 (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Finalists: Janet Jun-Lien Wong, 1987; 61233 (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Program Operation - AEJ, 1988; 61232 (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Finalists: Charisse K. Lawrence, 1988; 61231 (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - Finalists: John Yeh, AEJMC Applicant, 1988; 61230 (Box 13, Folder 42)